<topics>
  <topic>
    <id>https://guides.loc.gov/chronicling-america-alaska-purchase</id>
    <results>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1867-04-09/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Russian+Russia+Treaty+Empire+Seward</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Admiral Fox, on his return visit to Russia, told a friend in this city that Cortschakoff had said to him in St. Petersburg that the territory which Russia owned in America was not only valueless to his Government but was an expense and trouble which the Czar would gladly be rid of, and assured him that Russia would be willing to cede the territory to the United States as a gift if it were desirable to the Republic. This is certain. It is equally certain that Secretary Seward knew of the fact. Unfortunately for our Treasury and our tax-payers, there is no diplomatic glory to be got out of accepting a gift. To make a reputation out of an acquisition of territory ready to be handed over to us as a sheer measure of relief to the Russian exchequer, Mr. Seward had to negotiate for it, throw away $10,000,000 for it, mysteriously wrap up the transaction in a secret treaty, and suddenly appear in the Senate, after the expiration of the regular session of Congress, and urge the immediate approval of the treaty on the grounds, first: that the region to be acquired was relatively as valuable to Russia as Ireland is to England; that in climate and the natural wealth of timber, grain lands, fur-bearing animals, and fisheries, and probably coal, and gold, and silver, it was enormously valuable. Second: that if we did not immediately take it, we should lose the opportunity, and it would become the property of some other nation. Third: that the treaty must be ratified within 90 days or fail, and that if it failed, every Government in Europe would exult over its miscarriage, and our friendly relations with the powerful Russian Empire would be imperiled by the mortification to which we had subjected it throughout the world.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84026994/1867-04-12/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=Russian+Russia+Treaty+Alaska+gold+mines&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.355,-0.086,1.711,1.711,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82015486/1867-04-18/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=Value+Acquisition+Russia+Russian+Treaty+Treaty+Seward&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.248,-0.075,1.496,1.496,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85034039/1867-05-03/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Russia+Russian+Treaty+Gold+Seward&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.285,-0.079,1.571,1.571,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86053571/1867-12-24/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=Alaska+Russia+Russian+Treaty+Seward+Sitka&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.39,0.137,1.439,1.439,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83025293/1868-07-24/ed-1/?sp=6&amp;q=Boundless+Alaska+Russia+Russian+Treaty+Seward&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.206,-0.071,1.412,1.412,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>The House has voted the appropriation of $7,200,000 for Alaska, and it is now past doubt a Territory of the United States. The exchange of treaties took place June 20, 1867, and the money was to have been paid April 20, 1868, our military forces having, in the meantime, taken possession. It was feared that the failure of the House might lead to unpleasant complications with Russia, but that power which has manifested toward the United States, these many years, a friendly spirit, duly reciprocated, has not urged us. Mr. Butler endeavored to put a rider on the resolution withholding some half million dollars claimed to be due, we believe, a Massachusetts firm for munitions of war manufactured for Russia during the Crimean war, but the House rejected it. With the many, we believe the purchase of Alaska was inopportune, and yet accord that in many respects it is valuable to the United States. It loosens the hold of one great alien power from this continent; it places British Columbia in a position that renders its annexation to the United States desirable, perhaps essential to its welfare. We are absorbing the continent—that is America's destiny. It gives us 170,000 square miles of territory—larger than England, Ireland, Scotland, Wales, Denmark, Sweden, and Norway combined. It gives us four thousand miles of seacoast, with fine harbors and a coastline of 11,000, with fisheries ten times larger than those of the Atlantic. They last year sent twenty cargoes of fish, 22,366,000 pounds, into San Francisco. Mr. Johnson, of California, stated in the House, they would this year send ten times that amount, and in three years, with American enterprise, supply the markets of the world. It gives us great forests of ship timber, and the trade winds of the Pacific six months in the year bring the commerce of Asia along its shores, another additional argument for the Northern Pacific Railroad, by which it would save the distance from Puget Sound to San Francisco. Alaska may appear valueless now. It is only a few years since the half-continent west of the Missouri was so esteemed. It is considered valuable now. Alaska may not prove to have been a bad purchase, even though it was untimely. The government had purchased it; it had arisen.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86053571/1868-07-15/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=Alaska&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.29,-0.075,1.58,1.492,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86053571/1868-07-15/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=Alaska&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.29,-0.075,1.58,1.492,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84024828/1899-09-30/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Alaska+Alaskan+Field+Treasure+Cape+Nome+Gold</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>When Secretary Seward purchased Alaska from Russia in 1867 for $7,200,000, the anti-expansionists of that period ridiculed the transaction as a piece of supreme folly and the public generally agreed that he had bought nothing in particular except a few fur seals and a vast expanse of icebergs and glaciers.
          The commerce of Alaska for the year ending June 30, 1903, amounted to over $21,000,000, not including the gold output, which would add nearly $5,000,000 more. It is officially stated that since Alaska became American territory it has exported furs, fish, and gold in about equal values to the amount of $150,000,000, while investments of American capital in Alaska have reached $25,000,000. To this should be added considerable sums employed in furnishing transportation to Alaska. The same official authority estimates the aggregate shipments of merchandise to Alaska from the United States during the same period at $100,000,000. It takes something more than a few seals and icebergs to develop a commerce of such dimensions. That this is "only the small beginning of what is to follow in the not far distant future is my firm belief.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83020847/1868-03-14/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.304,-0.08,1.609,1.609,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn98059811/1906-03-24/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.353,-0.085,1.705,1.705,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>At this valuation of $7,200,000 the bargain could be deemed satisfactory even from the standpoint of the individual fisherman, miner, and wood-cutter; for the timber, mines, furs, and fisheries would easily yield the annual interest on that sum."
          "Now, as to the story of a secret arrangement about Alaska, in connection with the visit of the Russian fleet to the United States in 1863. This story is wholly imaginative fiction. It probably originated with those who had already made up their minds that the territory was worthless, and therefore that there must have been some occult reason for the purchase. In 1863 we had enough to do in trying to hold together such territory as the United States already had without attempting to add any more.</text>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn88056024/1916-02-27/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.217,-0.072,1.434,1.434,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn90052005/1917-10-11/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.249,-0.075,1.498,1.498,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83016244/1957-02-19/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.227,-0.073,1.454,1.454,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
      </results>
    </topic>
    <topic>
      <id>https://guides.loc.gov/chronicling-america-civil-war-ballooning</id>
      <results>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84026547/1861-05-28/ed-1/?sp=3&amp;q=Ballooning+balloons&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.201,-0.07,1.402,1.402,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>A Chance fob a Reputation. In view of the fact that our enemies intend to avail themselves of the superior advantages of balloons in the impending war to overlook the operations of the Confederate Army, it behooves the ruling powers of the South to profit by their example, and not be idle in this matter. In all the departments of Art and Science, the South can boast her superiors over the North. The military genius of the latter, for instance, cannot bear comparison with that of the former, and so in everything else. And now, in regard to this science that is to be tested in the coming contest the science of Ballooning, who is there in the whole breadth of the land, possesses such thorough, we may say perfect knowledge of the properties of the air—his native element—than the Aerologist of Petersburg, J. C. Patton, Esq. We answer without the fear of contradiction. None, no, not one. With commanding intelligence and eagle eye, a complete acquaintance with the subject in question, and an intrepid, daring disposition, he is the very man for the crisis. We beseech the Provisional Congress at Montgomery, to lose not a moment in engaging the services of Mr. Patton. He only waits his country's call. Pet. Express.
          </text>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85054845/1861-06-13/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=Balloon+ballooning&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.229,-0.073,1.458,1.458,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83035143/1861-06-21/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=balloon+Ballooning+ballooning&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.226,-0.073,1.452,1.452,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84026845/1861-11-27/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=balloon+corps&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.181,-0.068,1.362,1.362,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>Professor Lowe's balloon "Constitution" goes this afternoon to Beaufort, South Carolina, in the steamer Occur it Lion, which will tow the hull of the old steamer Washington Parke Custis, now called a balloon boat, carrying gas generators, sulphuric acid, and iron fillings, for making gas with other necessary concomitants. A balloon corps of forty privates, with a Corporal, Sergeant, Lieutenant, and Aeronaut, will form the expedition.</text>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83035216/1861-12-28/ed-1/?sp=4&amp;q=balloon+Ballooning&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.205,-0.071,1.41,1.41,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84028745/1862-01-24/ed-1/?sp=3&amp;q=Balloon+balloon+Ballooning+ballooning&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.23,-0.073,1.461,1.461,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84028083/1862-06-13/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=balloon+Ballooning+balloons&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.249,-0.075,1.498,1.498,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82015418/1862-09-04/ed-1/?sp=6&amp;q=balloon+BALLOON+Lowe+Professor&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.183,-0.068,1.366,1.366,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82015418/1862-09-04/ed-1/?sp=6&amp;q=balloon+BALLOON+Lowe+Professor&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.183,-0.068,1.366,1.366,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
            The use of the balloon as an auxiliary in warfare was introduced during the American Civil War. This innovative approach, employed during battles before Richmond, demonstrated the potential of aerial reconnaissance. A telegraph operator detailed their experience, where observations made from a balloon at 2,000 feet altitude were relayed directly to General McClellan and division commanders. This included identifying masked enemy batteries and providing coordinates for targeting. Additionally, the balloon facilitated communication over long distances, such as between the battlefield and Fortress Monroe, showcasing its strategic value. The observations from the balloon revealed troop movements, the impact of battles on Richmond’s streets, and the withdrawal of enemy forces, marking a significant advancement in military tactics.
          </text>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85033622/1864-04-20/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=ballooning+Ballooning+balloons&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.309,-0.009,1.618,1.618,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn90061417/1909-10-29/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.309,-0.081,1.618,1.618,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030213/1859-07-06/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.276,-0.078,1.552,1.552,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85025007/1859-07-08/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.263,-0.076,1.525,1.525,0</id>
        </result>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn90061556/1917-01-20/ed-1/?sp=3&amp;q=professor+lowe+civil+war+balloon&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.242,-0.074,1.485,1.485,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>Remnant of Only Confederate Balloon Discovered
            WASHINGTON. Tho aviation branch of the war department has Just
            received an interesting present In the shape of n piece of the only
            balloon owned by the Confederate array, which was made out of silk dresses
            contributed by the women of Rich
            mond during the siege of that city.
            This relic was found among the
            effects of the late Prof. T. S. C. Lowe,
            who was aeronaut of the Army of the
            Potomac during the Civil wnr. It was
            given to tho wnr department by his
            son, Leon P. Lowe of San Frnnclsco.
            Professor Lowe was the first
            aeronaut to take up Count Zeppelin
            and the flrst to take up a United
            States officer, General Helntzman.
            They looked Into Yorktown. Genernl
            McCIellan, who was In command of
            balloons used In the Crimean wnr, nnd so mnde use of them In his campaign,
            selecting Professor Lowe to command that branch.
            Tho captured Confederate balloon was under the command of Gen. E. P.
            Alexander with the Army of Northern Virginia. It made but one ascension
            nnd that not very successful. This balloon was towed down the James river
            by a tug.
            After the balloon wns captured, It was turned over to Professor Lowe for
            whatever use his department might mnke of It. Being of Impractical ma
            terials and construction, It was cut up and pieces given as souvenirs to promi
            nent persons of that day.</text>
          </result>
        </results>
        <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82016014/1898-08-20/ed-1/?dl=page&amp;sp=1&amp;q=professor+lowe+civil+war+balloon&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.146,-0.065,1.292,1.292,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
            About this time several other aeronauts, Professors La Mountain and Wise, offered their services to the government. The former was sent by General Butler to Fortress Monroe and the war department deciding to accept the services of an old experienced aeronaut, Lowe, on account of his youth, was displaced by Professor Wise, who continued with the army until about July 17 without special result. On Sunday morning, July 21, while the battle was in progress, Professor Lowe was instructed to inflate his balloon and report to headquarters at Manassas at once. The balloon was inflated at the Smithsonian grounds and towed toward the battlefield, which point was reached between 4 and 5 o'clock in the afternoon, meeting our retreating army. Waiting until all had passed, they began taking observations, which showed that the enemy was not following our retreating army and that only a few cavalry were visible. The balloon was then brought to Fort Corcoran, Arlington Heights. The following day (Monday) the wind blew fiercely, with a heavy rainstorm prevailing. On Tuesday morning the balloon was cut loose, traveling westward over the battlefield, where it was discovered that none of the enemy's troops were moving. Smoke showed that the troops were getting breakfast. Only a few scouting parties were seen.
          </text>
        </result>
      </topic>
      <topic>
        <id>https://guides.loc.gov/chronicling-america-enrico-caruso</id>
        <results>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1903-11-24/ed-1/?sp=9&amp;q=Opera+Enrico+Caruso&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.269,-0.077,1.538,1.538,0</id>
            <rel>0</rel>
          </result>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85042462/1905-04-19/ed-1/?sp=3&amp;q=Opera+Enrico+Caruso&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.238,-0.074,1.477,1.477,0</id>
            <rel>1</rel>
            <text>
              Caruso was the center of interest naturally, for he had come to the coast after a year of eastern triumphs that caused him to be acclaimed as the greatest of lyric tenors. That he more than justified all reports was generally acknowledged last night at the close of the opera, when the audience cheered and cheered, lingering under the spell of the tenor's voice and recalling the singer again and again. Men and women usually too conventional or too critical to applaud cried, "Bravo! Bravo!" and hundreds of handkerchiefs were waved from the boxes and parquet chairs. The duet at the close of the first act was received with an outburst of spontaneous applause and Caruso's appearance in the second act, when the sextette was sung, was the signal for a demonstration. The desire for a repetition of the sextette was ignored, although the applause lasted several minutes. In the last act, Caruso's triumph was complete. Los Angeles gave him a welcome that warmed his heart and sent him away with the desire to return to it often.
            </text>
          </result>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85042462/1906-11-17/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Caruso+Opera&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.244,-0.074,1.487,1.487,0</id>
            <rel>0</rel>
          </result>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84026749/1906-11-17/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Tenor+Caruso+Enrico+Arrest&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.215,-0.071,1.43,1.43,0</id>
            <rel>1</rel>
            <text>Enrico Caruso, the world's greatest tenor, was arrested in New York on a charge of disorderly and indecent conduct. The incident occurred at the Central Park Zoo, where Caruso was accused by a matron, Mrs. Hannah Graham, of behaving improperly while both were at the monkey house. After being arrested by a park officer, Caruso was taken to the police station and vehemently denied the accusations, describing his arrest as an outrage. He was later released on bail of $500, furnished by Heinrich Conried of the Metropolitan Opera House. The case was postponed due to Caruso reportedly suffering from sciatica.
            </text>
          </result>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn88085187/1909-07-13/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Caruso+Opera+Victor&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.207,-0.071,1.414,1.414,0</id>
            <rel>0</rel>
          </result>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1910-12-11/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Puccini+Caruso+Tenor+Enrico+Opera&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.29,-0.079,1.579,1.579,0</id>
            <rel>0</rel>
          </result>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1911-11-14/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Caruso+Opera+Victor&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.339,-0.084,1.677,1.677,0</id>
            <rel>0</rel>
          </result>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1921-08-03/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=Caruso+Opera+Enrico&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.208,-0.071,1.417,1.417,0</id>
            <rel>1</rel>
            <text>Enrico Caruso's operatic career exemplifies ceaseless study and resilience, winning him admiration worldwide. Despite facing personal and professional challenges, including illness and legal troubles, his unmatched talent and good nature cemented his legacy as one of the greatest tenors in history. Caruso's American debut at the Metropolitan Opera in 1903 marked the beginning of a transformative era for American opera, as he captivated audiences and significantly influenced the art form. His consistent performances and recordings further advanced the popularity of opera in the United States, making him a cultural icon whose impact endures.
            </text>
          </result>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1921-08-03/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=Caruso+Opera+Enrico&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.208,-0.071,1.417,1.417,0</id>
            <rel>1</rel>
            <text>Enrico Caruso's American debut at the Metropolitan Opera House in 1903 marked a pivotal moment in his career and had a transformative impact on American opera. His performances captivated audiences and established him as a cultural icon. Caruso's versatile repertoire, including his renowned renditions in "Rigoletto," "Pagliacci," and "Aida," elevated the prominence of opera in the United States. His recordings further popularized the art form, bringing opera into the homes of countless Americans. Caruso's immense talent, combined with his resilience and generosity, left a lasting legacy in the world of music, influencing artists and audiences alike.
            </text>
          </result>
          <result>
            <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn90066132/1921-08-02/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.224,-0.072,1.447,1.447,0</id>
            <rel>1</rel>
            <text>Enrico Caruso, world famous tenor, died here today, aged 48, following an operation performed Sunday. He arrived at Naples Sunday night and the specialists who were called in decided to operate immediately.
              New York, Aug. 2. The death of Enrico Caruso beneath the skies of his own Italy today caused sorrow on every highway and byway of New York. Here he was loved by all; the poor of East Side tenements; the wealthy of Fifth Avenue; the countless numbers who filled the seats of the Metropolitan Opera House whenever the incomparable tenor sang.
              Street sweepers stopped their work to mumble a prayer for the departed tenor; the cultured lamented the loss to art of one of its most cherished possessions. They felt the loss was not only America’s but the world’s. For Caruso’s superb tones have enraptured audiences the world around.</text>
            </result>
            <result>
              <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85054967/1917-03-17/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.316,-0.082,1.631,1.631,0</id>
              <rel>0</rel>
            </result>
            <result>
              <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83045211/1919-12-01/ed-1/?sp=4&amp;q=enrico+caruso%2C+opera%2C+tenor%2C+victor%2C+metropolitan+opera&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.204,-0.07,1.408,1.408,0</id>
              <rel>1</rel>
              <text>A musical program that presents such famous artists as Caruso, Gluck, Heifetz, Werrenrath and Zimbalist, is sure to stir the interest of the music-loving public.
              </text>
            </result>
            <result>
              <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84026749/1920-02-08/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.152,-0.065,1.304,1.304,0</id>
              <rel>0</rel>
            </result>
        </results>
    </topic>
</topics>
